ap.gov.in 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy – AP State Portal

### Privacy Policy

Thanks for visiting official State Portal of Andhra Pradesh (www.ap.gov.in) and reviewing our private policy.

**Personal Information :**

This portal does not automatically capture any specific personal information from you, (like name, phone number or e-mail address), that allows us to identify you individually.

Any Personal Information collected shall be used for the stated purpose and shall NOT be shared with any other third party (Public/private) and adequate security measures will be taken to protect your personal information. 

As part of our statistical analysis, this Portal gather certain information about the User, such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, domain name from which you access the Internet, the type of browser you use, operating system, the date and time of the visit and the pages visited, and the documents downloaded by you; the previous Internet address from which you linked directly to the site. We make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting our site unless an attempt to damage the site has been detected.

This Portal may contain links to other Government Departments/non Government sites whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. This Portal is not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these websites and encourages you to consult the Privacy notices of these sites.

This Portal provides some content presentation in Portable document format (.pdf files) and may add content for Download as and when need calls for. For the purpose, it requires programs on your computer for the usage. We recommends Adobe Reader and resources are available at their site for download/accessibility. However, this Portal held no responsibility or occurrences for the user thereof.

**E-mail Address/Feedback Forms :**

This portal calls for Email ids for Feedback and other interactive activities on the Portal. You may note that the Email Ids are collected as Identification in order to respond, forward to Departments, communicate for updates on Portal that may be of interest or to provide feedback better Portal presentation/or appreciation. Feedback forms serve the purpose for receiving Feedback/grievances/complaints from the users in a structured and formatted manner.
